<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Rimini</string>
    <string name="app_description">Rimini is an Italian municipality of approximately 150k inhabitants, located in the Emilia-Romagna italian region. The city is characterized by the presence of summer experiences of international relevance, with a coastline that extends for 15 km along the coast of the Adriatic sea. Rimini is colony founded by the Romans in 268 BC: for the entire period of the Roman domination it was a communication hub between the north and south of the peninsula, and on its soil the Roman emperors erected monuments of which important traces still remain today. It was the land of the Malatesta family: the court of Sigismondo Pandolfo Malatesta was one of the liveliest of the time, hosting artists such as Leon Battista Alberti and Piero della Francesca, and preserving important works of the Italian Renaissance.</string>
    <string name="general_address">%s Rimini, Italy</string>
    <string name="start_exploring">Start exploring!</string>
    <string name="navigate_up_button">Navigate Up button</string>



    <!-- Categories -->

    <string name="category_1_name">Lunch &amp; Dinner</string>
    <string name="category_2_name">Breakfast</string>
    <string name="category_3_name">Accommodation</string>
    <string name="category_4_name">Beach</string>
    <string name="category_5_name">Entertainment</string>
    <string name="category_6_name">Culture</string>



    <!-- LUNCH AND DINNER -->

    <string name="restaurant_1_name">La mi mama</string>
    <string name="restaurant_2_name">Osteria io e Simone</string>
    <string name="restaurant_3_name">Casina del bosco</string>
    <string name="restaurant_4_name">Dalla Lella</string>
    <string name="restaurant_5_name">Chi Burdlaz</string>
    <string name="restaurant_6_name">Na pizz</string>
    <string name="restaurant_7_name">La buca</string>
    <string name="restaurant_8_name">Sbionta</string>

    <string name="restaurant_1_rate">4.4</string>
    <string name="restaurant_2_rate">4.6</string>
    <string name="restaurant_3_rate">4.5</string>
    <string name="restaurant_4_rate">4.6</string>
    <string name="restaurant_5_rate">4.3</string>
    <string name="restaurant_6_rate">4.1</string>
    <string name="restaurant_7_rate">4.1</string>
    <string name="restaurant_8_rate">4.4</string>

    <string name="restaurant_1_address">Via Poletti 32, 47923</string>
    <string name="restaurant_2_address">Piazza Teatini 3, 47921</string>
    <string name="restaurant_3_address">Viale Beccadelli 15, 47921</string>
    <string name="restaurant_4_address">Via Covignano 96, 47923</string>
    <string name="restaurant_5_address">Viale Vespucci 63, 47921</string>
    <string name="restaurant_6_address">Via Flaminia 175, 47923</string>
    <string name="restaurant_7_address">Lungomare Tintori 5A, 47921</string>
    <string name="restaurant_8_address">Viale Vespucci 85, 47921</string>

    <string name="restaurant_1_description">La Mi Mama is the ideal place to experience relaxing moments, discovering the flavors and aromas of the ancient Romagna tradition. The fascinating bright space, the soft lights, the warm colours, the flowers, the furnishings, the sober accessories and the showcases full of fine wines, from the most renowned local and national companies, blend together giving diners a warm and particular atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_2_description">Very cute and welcoming place with warm lights that make you feel at home. Excellent product quality, impeccable service, great friendliness and kindness, fair prices.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_3_description">The true Piadina Romagnola is born in this fabulous territory. We prepare the piadina doughs by hand, with love, in our kitchen. We are a big family, many people who help each other with the aim of always giving the best to our guests and a vast amount of smiles.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_4_description">True Piadina made with hands and with the heart. Excellent piada, light and well filled. Many delicacies available, and also second courses that you can choose separately.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_5_description">Excellent service, waiters who go from table to table smiling, humming and being friendly. Food? When the ingredients are excellent, the result can only be excellent. Every dish releases the passion behind it, work, experience and love.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_6_description">Napizz is the most eccentric Italian food brand conceived, designed and created to amaze customers as if they were in a museum of contemporary pizza art. Napizz is Neapolitan sympathy, innovation and movement. Napizz is excellent raw materials and artisanal processing methods, continuous innovation to provide the customer with something unique.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_7_description">Since 1970, a few steps from the Port of Rimini, the elegant and refined La Buca Restaurant offers the ideal choice to sit at the table and enjoy unparalleled culinary specialities. Here you do not just eat, but you live an experience of taste, colors and flavors of seafood combined with the timeless recipes of the Romagna tradition.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_8_description">In Romagna, we know: if something is hot, it is not actually just hot, but "sbionta"! The sand fades under the scorching sun, the pan that comes out of the oven or the Piadina fades as soon as you remove it from the pan. This is why here, at Sbionta, you will find flavors that "sbiontano": Piadine, burgers and pizzas prepared on the spot, with quality raw materials and artisanal care. Because if it "sbionta" then it means that "it is done at the moment!"</string>



    <!-- BREAKFAST -->

    <string name="breakfast_1_name">Rinaldini</string>
    <string name="breakfast_2_name">Pascucci</string>
    <string name="breakfast_3_name">Caffè Ducale</string>
    <string name="breakfast_4_name">Caffè Cavour</string>
    <string name="breakfast_5_name">Embassy</string>

    <string name="breakfast_1_rate">4.1</string>
    <string name="breakfast_2_rate">4.0</string>
    <string name="breakfast_3_rate">4.7</string>
    <string name="breakfast_4_rate">4.3</string>
    <string name="breakfast_5_rate">4.3</string>

    <string name="breakfast_1_address">Viale Vespucci 8, 47921</string>
    <string name="breakfast_2_address">Viale Vespucci 3/A, 47921</string>
    <string name="breakfast_3_address">Corso D\'Augusto 222, 47921</string>
    <string name="breakfast_4_address">Piazza Cavour 12, 47921</string>
    <string name="breakfast_5_address">Viale Vespucci 33, 47921</string>

    <string name="breakfast_1_description">In just a few years, Roberto Rinaldini has been able to create an absolutely original, glamorous and elegant style, which stands out for his frequent "forays" into the fascinating world of fashion. A world he has always loved and from which he has been able to "steal" attention to detail and the search for stylistic perfection. Each of his desserts is conceived as a work in itself, a sartorial masterpiece whose basis, however, always remains the stubborn search for 360-degree quality: from the selection of raw materials to the processing techniques, up to the choice of packaging and sales environments.</string>
    <string name="breakfast_2_description">With a consolidated presence in various countries, Caffè Pascucci represents Italian excellence in the world of coffee. If your dream is to have your own coffee shop and pursue quality, our formats are for you. For generations, Pascucci has been dedicated to creating unique experiences through coffee. Our passion for the art of coffee and commitment to sustainability make us a distinctive brand on the international scene.</string>
    <string name="breakfast_3_description">What you have the pleasure of tasting at Ducale is the highest version of the famous drink, carefully prepared by the owner\'s skill, which is also expressed in the supply of raw materials and in the story of the various blends, with freshly ground beans and with origins ranging from the Indies, Africa and Latin America.</string>
    <string name="breakfast_4_description">Caffè Cavour is one of the historic bars in Rimini with internal lounges where you can read the newspapers: it is one of the most elegant bars in Rimini, with very good coffee and an awesome italian mood.</string>
    <string name="breakfast_5_description">One of the most beautiful testimonies of Italian Liberty architecture has been returned to Rimini, to the people of Rimini, to everyone. With Embassy, a new chapter in an 80-year history. The cult venue worthy of the 50s and 60s which hosted legends such as Mina, Ornella Vanoni, Giorgio Gaber, Walter Chiari, Lucio Battisti and Fred Buscaglione, presents itself in a new guise, weaving new connections. Embassy Restaurant is a multifunctional and transversal space where food, culture and music mix and contaminate each other.</string>



    <!-- ACCOMMODATION -->

    <string name="hotel_1_name">Grand Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotel_2_name">Hotel Sporting</string>
    <string name="hotel_3_name">Hotel Imperiale</string>
    <string name="hotel_4_name">Hotel Ambasciatori</string>
    <string name="hotel_5_name">Hotel Villa Adriatica</string>
    <string name="hotel_6_name">i-SUITE</string>

    <string name="hotel_1_rate">4.0</string>
    <string name="hotel_2_rate">4.5</string>
    <string name="hotel_3_rate">4.5</string>
    <string name="hotel_4_rate">4.5</string>
    <string name="hotel_5_rate">4.5</string>
    <string name="hotel_6_rate">5.0</string>

    <string name="hotel_1_address">Parco Federico Fellini, 47921</string>
    <string name="hotel_2_address">Viale Vespucci 20, 47921</string>
    <string name="hotel_3_address">Viale Vespucci 16, 47921</string>
    <string name="hotel_4_address">Viale Vespucci 22, 47921</string>
    <string name="hotel_5_address">Viale Vespucci 3, 47921</string>
    <string name="hotel_6_address">Viale Regina Elena 28, 47921</string>

    <string name="hotel_1_description">A symbol of the sweet life and, above all, the place of Fellini\'s imagination: the 5-star Grand Hotel Rimini has always been a myth of holiday resorts. You too can become part of the legend. Grand Hotel Rimini is a journey through time to discover a land with profound traditions and strong suggestions. Let yourself be fascinated by a beach holiday that, both in summer and out of season, can arouse rich emotions.</string>
    <string name="hotel_2_description">Are you looking for a hotel in Rimini? Whatever the reason for your stay at Riviera Romagnola, whether it is a beach holiday or a business trip, by taking advantage of this 4-star offer at the best price you will be able to enjoy all the comforts of the Sporting hotel at the cheapest price available.</string>
    <string name="hotel_3_description">Around you elegance, refinement, and the uniqueness of a 4-star hotel experience. In front, only the sea. Rimini, in Marina Centro, imagines a place for relaxing and tasting moments, in a wellness break with the view of the sea, all in a single 5-floors environment. When a hotel becomes a fascinating experience.</string>
    <string name="hotel_4_description">At the 4-star Hotel Ambasciatori, tradition has always married elegance for a quality welcome characterized by style and class. Hotel Ambasciatori is among the most popular hotels in Rimini: for business trips, corporate meetings, relaxing weekends or splendid seaside holidays!</string>
    <string name="hotel_5_description">In the heart of Rimini\'s Marina Centro there is an ancient jewel, a 4-star historic residence that has welcomed its guests since 1880 in an atmosphere of ancient elegance. Hotel Villa Adriatica in Rimini has seen the city change face and become one of the best known and loved tourist destinations for those who want a seaside stay full of services.</string>
    <string name="hotel_6_description">A new concept of boutique hotel in Rimini, a design object, a wonderful architecture. A unique, unusual and disruptive place, where time expands into precious eternal moments to dedicate to self-care, to small things, to scents, to sensations. The 5-star modern hotel in Rimini.</string>



    <!-- BEACH -->

    <string name="beach_1_name">Tiki Bagno 26</string>
    <string name="beach_2_name">Libra Beach</string>
    <string name="beach_3_name">Rimini Dog No Problem</string>
    <string name="beach_4_name">Bagni Ricci</string>
    <string name="beach_5_name">Adriatic Village</string>

    <string name="beach_1_rate">4.4</string>
    <string name="beach_2_rate">4.5</string>
    <string name="beach_3_rate">4.4</string>
    <string name="beach_4_rate">4.5</string>
    <string name="beach_5_rate">4.6</string>

    <string name="beach_1_address">Lungomare Tintori 30A, 47921</string>
    <string name="beach_2_address">Lungomare Di Vittorio 8B, 47921</string>
    <string name="beach_3_address">Lungomare Di Vittorio 28A, 47924</string>
    <string name="beach_4_address">Lungomare Spadazzi 141–143, 47924</string>
    <string name="beach_5_address">Lungomare Murri 8, 47921</string>

    <string name="beach_1_description">In the heart of Riviera Romagnola, you will find friendliness, high quality services and lots of comfort. Like every year, we are the favorite destination for people who want to spend entire days of sun and sea in the name of relaxation.</string>
    <string name="beach_2_description">With approximately 25 thousand square-meters of extension, Libra Beach is one of the largest and most innovative beaches in the entire Riviera Romagnola; it also has an area reserved for suites widely spaced apart, to relax in complete peace. The animation staff takes care of the children\'s entertainment in the Baby Park. The offer of high quality services is completed with the two chiringuitos by the sea (Kokale 63 and Maina), the Gym, the Nautical Center and the Swimming School.</string>
    <string name="beach_3_description">Our beach is made up of two beach establishments which are located next to each other: Bagno 81 No Problem, a family beach where there is a beach service for customers without dogs and the Rimini Dog No Problem dog beach, which is instead located at Bagno 82 and where it is possible to take dogs to the beach.</string>
    <string name="beach_4_description">Do you know what is the only beach in Rimini that offers you a complete sea-based holiday? It is the Bagni Ricci beach. Since 1946 the Ricci family, a historic family of fishermen from Rimini, has lived and worked by the sea with one single goal: to make you feel good with your feet on the sand. Special dishes await you, while your feet are on the sand!</string>
    <string name="beach_5_description">The Adriatic Village bathing establishment (beaches 35, 36, 37) is located in Marina Centro, on the Rimini seafront. The beach, clean, well-kept and very spacious, offers the possibility of enjoying moments of relaxation and more. Adriatic Village is the right choice for everyone: families, couples, friends or for solitary moments. The beach is equipped with numerous sunbeds and umbrellas, with a proposal dedicated to the comfort of each of our guests.</string>



    <!-- ENTERTAINMENT -->

    <string name="entertainment_1_name">Coconuts</string>
    <string name="entertainment_2_name">Carnaby</string>
    <string name="entertainment_3_name">Turquoise Beach Club</string>
    <string name="entertainment_4_name">Altromondo</string>
    <string name="entertainment_5_name">Boabay</string>
    <string name="entertainment_6_name">Fiabilandia</string>

    <string name="entertainment_1_rate">3.7</string>
    <string name="entertainment_2_rate">3.8</string>
    <string name="entertainment_3_rate">3.8</string>
    <string name="entertainment_4_rate">4.2</string>
    <string name="entertainment_5_rate">4.0</string>
    <string name="entertainment_6_rate">4.1</string>

    <string name="entertainment_1_address">Lungomare Tintori 5, 47921</string>
    <string name="entertainment_2_address">Via Brindisi 20, 47924</string>
    <string name="entertainment_3_address">Lungomare Tintori 6, 47921</string>
    <string name="entertainment_4_address">Via Flaminia 358, 47924</string>
    <string name="entertainment_5_address">Via Delle Officine 24, 47923</string>
    <string name="entertainment_6_address">Via Cardano 15, 47924</string>

    <string name="entertainment_1_description">Coconuts is the right place to spend a special evening in company with your friends. The disco is open all year round, in winter there is dancing in the internal rooms, while in summer the events move to the Rimini seafront, a few steps from the beach.</string>
    <string name="entertainment_2_description">The Carnaby Club is a historic 3-floors disco in Rimini that inaugurated its floors in 1968. In its history, it has gone through all the fashions, following musical evolution and always confirming itself as the protagonist of the coastal nights. Despite its longevity, however, it has never lost its freshness, nor has it ever changed the values it believes in: it has always remained faithful to its identity as a friendly, strongly international place, made up of people, smiles, enthusiasm, and dedicated to clean fun.</string>
    <string name="entertainment_3_description">Our aim? make you live every day as if you were on holiday. 350 umbrellas, suites, sports fields, bar, restaurant, Chiringuito, relaxation areas and much more. Entertainment every evening with events, shows and DJ sets.</string>
    <string name="entertainment_4_description">Altromondo Studios represents the progenitor of nightclubs history in Riccione and Rimini. With the first opening in 1967 it introduced a great change in the world of nightlife, becoming the point of reference for local inhabitants and tourists on holiday in Rimini and Riccione. This work has led the Club to play a central role in the national and international entertainment scene, continuing to attract the biggest names in the world dance scene such as Hardwell, Steve Aoki, Afrojack, Deorro, Nicky Romero, Timmy Trumpet and other great talents.</string>
    <string name="entertainment_5_description">Slides, tunnels, inclined ramps, trampolines, platforms, a gigantic iceberg to climb and many other fun and adrenaline-filled inflatables. And, in addition, a space dedicated to children which they can access accompanied by an adult.</string>
    <string name="entertainment_6_description">A beautiful park made up of simple and magical attractions suitable for the whole family, especially if you have small children, ideal for spending a carefree day with the family.</string>



    <!-- CULTURE -->

    <string name="culture_1_name">Arco di Augusto</string>
    <string name="culture_2_name">Ponte di Tiberio</string>
    <string name="culture_3_name">Tempio Malatestiano</string>
    <string name="culture_4_name">Castel Sismondo</string>
    <string name="culture_5_name">Vecchia Pescheria</string>
    <string name="culture_6_name">Domus del Chirurgo</string>
    <string name="culture_7_name">Fellini Museum</string>

    <string name="culture_1_rate">4.6</string>
    <string name="culture_2_rate">4.9</string>
    <string name="culture_3_rate">4.6</string>
    <string name="culture_4_rate">4.6</string>
    <string name="culture_5_rate">4.6</string>
    <string name="culture_6_rate">4.5</string>
    <string name="culture_7_rate">4.6</string>

    <string name="culture_1_address">Corso D\'Augusto, 47921</string>
    <string name="culture_2_address">Corso D\'Augusto, 47921</string>
    <string name="culture_3_address">Via IV Novembre 35, 47921</string>
    <string name="culture_4_address">Piazza Malatesta, 47923</string>
    <string name="culture_5_address">Piazza Cavour, 47921</string>
    <string name="culture_6_address">Piazza Ferrari, 47921</string>
    <string name="culture_7_address">Piazza Malatesta, 47923</string>

    <string name="culture_1_description">Built in 27 BC with Istrian stone, in honor of Caesar Octavian Augustus, it is the oldest of the surviving Roman arches and stands at the arrival point of the Via Flaminia (which connected Rome to Rimini). The architecture is enhanced by a rich decorative apparatus, full of political and propagandistic meanings. The opening of the fornix, so wide that it could not be closed by doors, recalled the peace achieved after a long period of civil wars.</string>
    <string name="culture_2_description">An imposing architectural work from the Roman era, the bridge was built over the Marecchia river by decree of the Emperor Augustus and its completion is due to his successor Tiberius (14–21 AD). Made of Istrian stone, with five arches, in Doric style, it represents one of the most notable surviving Roman bridges. The bridge marks the beginning of the consular streets, Emilia and Popilia, heading to the North and is located at the end of the main historic street of the city, Corso D\'Augusto.</string>
    <string name="culture_3_description">Testimony of the Malatesta magnificence, it was Sigismondo Pandolfo Malatesta who ordered the works for the transformation of the ancient Romanesque-Gothic church of Saint Francesco into a splendid monument in harmony with the new Renaissance culture. Work on the temple began in 1450. The exterior is the work of the great genius Leon Battista Alberti and presents a majestic facade (unfinished in the upper part) inspired by the shapes of the Roman triumphal arch. The entire construction rests on a high base in Istrian stone, framed by cords taken from the base of Arco D\'Augusto.</string>
    <string name="culture_4_description">Sigismondo began its construction on 20 March 1437. The castle was conceived as a palace and fortress at the same time, as a worthy seat for the court and the garrison, and as a sign of power and supremacy over the city. The construction retains a notable charm, with its large square towers and powerful walls, whose original effect, when they rose from the deep moat, must have been formidable, comparable, due to their inclination and grandeur, to pyramids.</string>
    <string name="culture_5_description">Built by Giovan Francesco Buonamici in 1747, it reflects the economic importance of fishing in Rimini. It appears as a two-order lodge opened by three round arches; at the corners four statuettes of dolphins with a jet of water (the fountains for cleaning the fish). Inside there were long benches made of Istrian stone, where women sold the clams.</string>
    <string name="culture_6_description">At the end of 1980, during street furniture works in the central Piazza Ferrari, an archaeological site of extraordinary importance was discovered, with evidence from the Roman age to the Middle Ages. In the area, close to the walls of Ariminum, not far from the ancient port, stood the "Domus del Chirurgo" (surgeon\'s house), so-called from the profession of the last owner, a doctor of Greek culture. Since 2007, Domus Del Chirurgo has been open to the public, a small Pompeii re-emerged from the darkness of the centuries in the historic heart of Rimini.</string>
    <string name="culture_7_description">The Fellini Museum is a widespread museum center of a very new concept and the largest museum project dedicated to Federico Fellini. Three spaces are involved: Castel Sismondo, Palazzo del Fulgor and Piazza Malatesta. A space of creativity - included by the Ministry of Culture among the major national cultural heritage projects - in the name of Fellini\'s visionary nature, of cinema, of the relationship with the arts, in permanent dialogue between innovation and tradition.</string>

</resources>